Philipp B Moser

1401 Merrill Creek Parkway Apt 1037, Everett, WA 98126 (630) 401-5885 | Philipp.B.Moser@gmail.com

OBJECTIVES: To be an active employee who contributes to the mission, vision, and values of the company, and to interact on a professional level with other employees. To give excellent performance, and to translate my experience, knowledge, skills, and abilities, into value for organization.

SKILLS

- Trilingual (Spanish, German)
- Attention to Detail
- Communication
- Time Management

- Supervision
- Leadership
- Fast Learning
- Punctuality

EDUCATION

Lake Park High School 2007-2011 590 S Medinah Rd, Roselle, IL 60172

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Washington State Department of Transportation, Seattle, WA

Bridge Maintenance Specialist 2: 40+ hrs/week 01/2021-08/2021

- Welding of movable bridge decks plates.
- Concrete injections
- Operating 42-foot boat
- Routine bridge inspection for repair
- Monitoring of flooding systems, and fire hydrant systems

Union Pacific Railroad, Melrose Park, IL

Carman Freight Welder; 40+ hrs/week

10/2017 - 08/2019

- Number one responsibility was safety.
- Duties included: repairing, inspecting, and painting freight cars.
- Performed class 1 air brake tests on outbound trains.
- Held a Leadman position for the inbound yard of Proviso.

United States Marine Corps, Jacksonville, NC

Heavy Equipment Operator; 50+ hrs/week 07/2011-07/2015

- Maintained proper working hours and miles, discrepancies, and updated repairs to the vehicle.
- Counseled junior Marines on Job skilled deficiencies.
- Maintained accountability of 3-million-dollar vehicle and maintained vehicle at one hundred percent readiness at all times.